[{"answer": "I said Barbra.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Did you say \"Barbara\"?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I took a class in it, yeah.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "How did you even know to buy a sports jacket?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Oh, if you like -- yeah.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "You also had a ball doing it, didn't you?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Do you hate all work, basically?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I love -- I love making movies and I love recording.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What do you like doing?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Uh-huh.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "You consider yourself to be primarily an actress who sings, right?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "The dream was always to be an actress, to be a star?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think when I was younger, I wanted to be a star, until I became a star, and then it's a lot of work.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "You wanted to be a star?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I saw that parallel, yeah.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "I think it did scar me more than it drove me.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "How much do you think it scarred you or did it just drive you?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Have you been able to find out a lot about him and his character and his life?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "That he was telling me something.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "It was this message that, you know, no matter what, love is the answer.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "What was he telling you?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "You didn't ask how long it lasted.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Does the wider world know all of them?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Oh, maybe seven.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "How long does it need to last to qualify for proper love, do you think?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I think -- and I think you'd become -- I'm sure you are the same, but you are parentally curious, because you never knew this person, who yet despite that, was such a pivotal part of your life, clearly.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "But there is something that you recognize in someone's past, and it's -- it's a void, that you're recognizing, don't you think?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "She was a wonderful singer.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Or was there a sense always of jealousy that you were leading the kind of life, perhaps, she dreamt of herself?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Basically, yeah.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Did you feel that you had reconciled things with her?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "It was something that she made a record of when she -- when I was 13 and she took me, but it was really because she made the record and then I was able to make the record when I was 13.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Do you remember?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "You know what it was, I used to say, ma, how come you never told me, \"I love you\", you never said those words or really hugged me.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Do you think she was proud of you?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Oh, I just -- I think everything he does is great.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "How are you with your son?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Doesn't he have a gorgeous voice?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Have you never seen it?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "-- Redford that when he came in.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "It was just a very interesting story about through their daughter and her political activism at Berkeley in 1968 and the Democratic National Convention, which is very interesting.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What would have happened?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "You did.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "I kept sending you articles, right?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "No, no, no, I don't have a horse in the race.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Your man didn't?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Oh, my God, no.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "My argument with you was I wondered whether Mitt Romney could be better for the American economy?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "You were having none of it.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "No, you know why?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I can't even imagine thinking about what would happen to the Supreme Court if a Republican were the president, you know.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Why have you been so consistent in support of Obama?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Because the people -- the people are getting smarter, they are going, I don't like this -- all this amount of money spent on this election.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What does that tell you about the American people?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Have you ever been in love with a Republican?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Could you ever be?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Or I imagine one of them when he came out so vocally for gay rights, finally?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yeah, that you are particularly proud of.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What else has he done, are you saying?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I thought that pretty unsettling.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "That's so scary, isn't it?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Some men, mostly women, right?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, we are one of the last countries to ever think of having a woman be president, but I think that's possible now.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "You feel that there is any form of real equality yet in America for women?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I don't know, but I hope after a four-year rest that she would run.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Do you think Hillary is likely to run?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I want to know who you think the greatest movie star in the world is, ever.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "It is?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I'm so objective when I look at myself.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Yeah, when you look at yourself?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Not particularly.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Do you see a beautiful woman there?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "From certain angles.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Have you ever looked in the mirror and thought you look beautiful?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, my left.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Which is your best angle?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Because my eyes don't look as cross-eyed sometimes or my nose is better, my--", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I don't trust most people.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Have you resisted the sort of self-masticated plunge into plastic surgery that so many American female stars feel compelled to do?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Marlon Brando.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Who do you think?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Oh, no question.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "No, I don't, actually.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Do you doubt that?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "He called me up once, and said, sing me a song.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Marlon Brando would?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "And what did you have to sing?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I sang a song called \"Nobody's Heart Belongs to Me.\"", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What did you sing him?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "I don't remember that.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "What did he say at the end of it?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "He wanted to take me to the desert, to see the wild flowers.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Where did you go?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yeah, I thought, yes.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "You turned down Marlon Brando?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "He was fine.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "How did he take rejection?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes, because it's just almost, I would say, musical perfection.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "I can't see what you see, I really can't.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "What do you feel when you see it?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "27 years.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "And forgot the words to a few big songs, and it freaked you out so much, you did not perform again live for how long?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "What the hell is a diva, I don't even know.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Have you even been a terrible diva?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Have you ever been one?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, I screamed at people.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Have you ever screamed at people?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I am proud to say I am.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Are you a perfectionist?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I think more so now, I can relax.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Are you a naturally person, or can you just completely relax if you want to?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "You want to drive cross-country with me?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "No, it was just a thought, and if you don't want to do it, then fine, I don't want to push you.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "TREISAND: Don't you think I might get on your nerves a little bit?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Yeah, I could imagine going it with him.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Could you ever imagine doing a road trip with your son like that for a week?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Yeah, because we're just too similar.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "You know what that is?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "It actually brings us closer.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "How did they go?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "Well, it's not conscious.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "Did you think that?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Every once in a while.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Do you ever look at it and think, yes, I've not done badly for a young girl from Brooklyn?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "It's not a challenge, put it that way.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Did you like making that?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "I'm 47.", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 813, "question": "47?", "qSentId": 812}, {"answer": "Yes!", "docId": "121223pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "When you were a baby, you wanted to do an interview with me?", "qSentId": 816}]